MIRON AUSLANDER

Visual Effects & Motion Graphics Artist

www.mironauslander.com

ABOUT

Visual Effects and Motion Graphics creator with over 15 years of experience in the Israeli entertainment and content industry. Specializing in creating advanced visual effects for television series, cinema, commercials, and digital content. Full command of video language and cutting-edge technologies in the field.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Visual Effects & Motion Graphics Artist | Freelance

2010 - Present

Leading and executing complex projects in visual effects and motion graphics, from concept to final delivery.

Leading Television Series

- Fauda Season 1 (Israeli Academy Television Award 2015 Special Effects)
- Hostages Season 1+2 (Israeli Academy Television Award 2013 Special Effects)
- The Truth
- Roch Tsonit (8200)
- Hazarot (Returns)
- HaShoter HaTov (The Good Cop)

Reality Television

- Big Brother Israel
- The Voice Israel
- The Amazing Race Israel
- Survival (Hisardut)
- Ninja Israel

Digital & Branding Projects

- Meta (Facebook/Instagram) Advertising project for brand
- Intel Israel Corporate and promotional content
- Microsoft Teams Israel Internal use Explainer Video

Offline Editor

2009 - 2010

- MasterChef Israel Offline Editing
- · The Amazing Race Israel Offline Editing
- Mechubarim (Connected) Offline Editing

Assistant Editor

2008 - 2009

- "Sipur Gadol" (Big Story) Einat Glazer Zarhin (Production)
- "HaBorer" (The Arbitrator) Itzik Tzhaki (Production)

Editing Technician / Digitizer | Post House

2006 - 2008

Worked on various projects in a professional post-production environment, operating and maintaining advanced editing systems.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Professional Software

- Compositing & VFX: Adobe After Effects, DaVinci Resolve Fusion
- 3D & Rendering: Cinema 4D, Redshift
- Tracking & Matchmoving: Mocha Pro, pfTrack
- Editing: Adobe Premiere Pro, Avid Media Composer
- **Suite:** Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator)

Emerging Technologies:

- Generative AI for VFX (ComfyUI, Runway, Stable Diffusion, Midjourney)
- Al-powered audio tools (ElevenLabs)
- Al workflow optimization

Core Competencies

- Compositing & Visual Effects
- Motion Graphics & Animation
- 3D Modeling & Rendering
- Tracking & Matchmoving
- Color Grading & Finishing
- Post-Production Workflow

AWARDS & RECOGNITION

- Y 2015 Israeli Academy Television Award Special Effects Fauda

EDUCATION

Film Studies - Midrasha School of Art, Beit Berl College

LANGUAGES

- Hebrew Native
- English Fluent